<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="category_views">Places</string>
    <string name="category_temple">Temple</string>
    <string name="category_shops">Shops</string>
    <string name="category_college">College</string>
    <string name="blueworld">Blue World, one of the biggest theme park, established by Blue World Corporation Pvt. Ltd., is located at Mandhana - Bithoor Road, just a stones throw distance from Mandhan Circle, just 22 k.m. away from Central Station. Blue World accompanies exceptionally structured and well planned, aesthetically illuminated restaurants, dry rides, water slides, theming and many more attractions. </string>
    <string name="Iskcon">Beautifully constructed with plenty of parking space, nice maintained lawns as usual very clean iskon temple. Small canteen also available for snacks etc. Along with darshan of almighty, a beautiful place for nice evening.</string>
    <string name="motijheel">Moti Jheel is a lake and drinking water reservoir in the Benajhabar area of Kanpur, which together with its adjoining gardens and childrens park is an important tourist attraction. </string>
    <string name="jktemple">JK Temple is a temple in the Indian city of Kanpur. It is considered to be a unique blend of ancient and modern architecture. The mandapa of the temple has been constructed with high roof for adequate ventilation of light and air.</string>
    <string name="ravanatemple">Ravana temple is one of its kind in Kanpur. Ravana, who was a follower of Lord Shiva is worshipped here as the patron diety . Every year during Dussehra huge celebrations add to the festivity and millions of devotees visit this shrine to worship Ravana.</string>
    <string name="pankihanuman">Hindu temple dating back to circa 1600, with white towers, 3 entrances and a Hanuman shrine.</string>
    <string name="greenpark">Green Park Stadium is a 60,000 capacity floodlit multi-purpose stadium located in Kanpur, India, and the Uttar Pradesh cricket team.[2] The stadium is under the control of the Sports Department Uttar Pradesh. It is the only international cricket stadium in Uttar Pradesh that has regularly hosted international cricket matches in both Test and One Day format.</string>
    <string name="nanarao">Nana Rao Park / Company Bagh is a public city park in Kanpur city, the industrial hub of Uttar Pradesh in North India build after Indian Independence in honor of Nana Sahib. </string>
    <string name="zsquare">Z Square Mall is a shopping mall cum entertainment complex in Indian city of Kanpur. The mall is spread on an area of five acres in the middle of the Kanpur city with 1,500,000 sqft. of built-up area and presence of more than 150 National and International brands</string>
    <string name="ravemoti">Rave@Moti is a Multiplex cum Mall in the Indian city of Kanpur. The mall is spread over an area of 2.50 Lac sq. ft and consists of three multiplexes by Adlabs, two restaurants, Tadka – Indian cuisine, Palate – Multicuisine, a banquet hall named Jalsaa, Food Court.</string>
    <string name="sisamau">One of the oldest markets in the city, it is very conjusted. One must be mentally prepared to walk a lot as the shops are scattered and are in narrow lanes. One of the best markets for footwears and clothes.</string>
    <string name="mallroad">The Mall Road is one of the most popular tourist attractions in Kanpur that enfolds many hotels, restaurants, clubs, bars, banks, shops, offices, post offices, and tourist offices. People can walk up and down the Mall road slowly and enjoy the scenic views of the nature</string>
    <string name="csjm">Chhatrapati Shahu Ji Maharaj University, formerly Kanpur University, is a public state university located in Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh, India. It is administered under the state legislature of the government of Uttar Pradesh.</string>
    <string name="hbti">Harcourt Butler Technical University is a government technical university located at Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh in India. The HBTU was named after Sir Spencer Harcourt Butler, governor of the United Provinces in British India.</string>
    <string name="gsvm">Ganesh Shankar Vidyarthi Memorial Medical College is a state-run medical college in Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh. The college is named after Ganesh Shankar Vidyarthi, a freedom fighter and journalist from Kanpur. It was founded in 1956. </string>
    <string name="iitk">Established in 1960 as one of the first Indian Institutes of Technology, the institute was created with the assistance of a consortium of nine US research universities as part of the Kanpur Indo-American Programme (KIAP).[</string>
    <string name="college1">Indian Institute of Technology Kanpur</string>
    <string name="college2">Chhatrapati Shahu Ji Maharaj University</string>
    <string name="college3">Harcourt Butler Technical University</string>
    <string name="college4">Ganesh Shankar Vidyarthi Memorial Medical College</string>
    <string name="add1">Kalyanpur, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add2">Kalyanpur GT Road, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add4">Swarup Nagar, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add3">Nawabganj, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="shop1">Z Square</string>
    <string name="shop2">Rave Moti</string>
    <string name="shop3">Sisamau</string>
    <string name="shop4">Mall Road</string>
    <string name="add5">Bada Chauraha, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add6">Rawatpur, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add7">Garib Chowki, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add8">Mall Road, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="temple1">Panki Mandir</string>
    <string name="temple2">ISKCON Kanpur</string>
    <string name="temple3">Shri Radhakrishna Temple</string>
    <string name="temple4">Ravana Temple</string>
    <string name="add9">Panki, Kanpur 208020</string>
    <string name="add10">Bithoor Road , Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add11">near to R.T.O. office, Kanpur 208005</string>
    <string name="add12">Shiwala, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="View1">Blue World Theme Park</string>
    <string name="View2">Nana Rao Park</string>
    <string name="View3">Green Park</string>
    <string name="View4">Moti Jheel</string>
    <string name="add14">Mandhana-Bithoor Road, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add15">Bithoor, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add16">Green Park, Kanpur</string>
    <string name="add17">Near Kamala Retreat And Moti Park, Kanpur</string>
</resources>
